(Raj:)It's called being nice.
(Sheldon:)Okay, if you think being nice
will get him to shut up, I'll try it.
You know what, guys, never mind.
(Howard:)I just won't talk about the greatest
achievement of my life ever again.
(Sheldon:)Look at that, the problem solved itself.
(Leonard:)Hello, boys.
(Sheldon:)What if we were to go
as dinner table favorites, salt and pepper?
(Amy:)You know salt makes me retain water...
(Amy:)...and my cousin, William, was ground
to death in a pepper factory accident.
(Amy:)Raggedy Ann and Andy?
I loved them growing up.
(Sheldon:)I don't think so. Those dolls represent
three things I don't care for:
Clowns, children, and raggedyness.
(Sheldon:)- I think it's a lost cause.
- No.